const dayFourQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Which verse of the Quran is the longest?",
    options: ["Q2:255", "Q2:282", "Q2:187", "Q4:12", "Q5:3"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which ‘Surah’ (Chapter) of the Quran falls at the middle of Quran?",
    options: [
      "Suratul Yasin",
      "Suratul Israil",
      "Suratul Kahf",
      "Surau Maryam",
      "Sutau Taaha",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "How many chapters do we have in the Quran?",
    options: ["6666", "313", "114", "60", "30"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Chapter of the Quran is it that Allaah mentioned Battle of Badr?",
    options: [
      "Suratut Taobah",
      "Suratul Baqarah",
      "Suratul Anfal",
      "Suratul Ahzab",
      "Suratun Nisaa",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "On how many modes (or letters) was the Quran revealed?",
    options: [
      "one modes",
      "two modes",
      "three modes",
      "five modes",
      "seven modes",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Two chapters of Quran; one start with the last word of the second, what are their names?",
    options: [
      "Suratul Infitar and Suratul Nabai",
      "Suratul Naml and Suratul Qari’ah",
      "Suratul Qadr and Suratul Fajr",
      "Suratul Kahf and Suratul Ikhlas",
      "Suratul Muzammil and Suratul Rum",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which verse of the Quran highly comprises the name 'Allah'?",
    options: ["Q2:255", "Q2:282", "Q2:187", "Q4:12", "Q5:3"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the only woman whose real name was mentioned in the holy Quran?",
    options: [
      "‘Aisha bint Abubakr",
      "Maryam bint ‘Imran",
      "Fatimah bint Muhammad",
      "‘Asiya bint Muzahim",
      "Hannah bint Faqud",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Chapter of the Quran caused the conversion of Umar bn Khatab (May Allaah be pleased with him) to Islam?",
    options: [
      "Suratul Yasin",
      "Suratul Israil",
      "Suratul Kahf",
      "Suratul Maryam",
      "Suratul Taaha",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What is longest word of the Quran?",
    options: [
      "Walyatalatof",
      "yasaluunaka",
      "fajama’naaum",
      "Fa asqaynakumuuh",
      "Fasayakfiikahumuuh",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many Chapters of the Quran started with the letter Tah Sin Min?",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was first to order the compilation of Quran?",
    options: [
      "Abubakr Sidiq",
      "Umar bn Khattab",
      "‘Uthman bn ‘Affan",
      "Ali bn Abi Talib",
      "‘Abdullahi bn Mas’ud",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "For how many years was the Quran revealed?",
    options: ["63 years", "40 years", "23 years", "13 years", "10 years"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Where was the first verses of the Quran revealed to the Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him)?",
    options: [
      "In Ka’bah",
      "at ‘Arafah",
      "in the cave of Najwah",
      "in the cave of Hirah",
      "in the room of Khadijah",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the last Chapter of the Quran, according to its arrangement?",
    options: [
      "Suratul Fatiha",
      "Suratun Nas",
      "Suratul Ikhlas",
      "Suratul Baqarah",
      "Suratul Fatih",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
];

export default dayFourQuestions;
